Guide to the Brooklyn, N.Y., Department of Law, Corporation Counsel records 2013.015
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Correspondence, 1866-1913; 2.5 linear feet; in 6 manuscript boxes
  - Dalton, William (Commissioner of Water Supply), 1891 (Box 217, Folder 36)
  - Commissioners of Electrical Subways, 1893 (Box 217, Folder 37)
  - Mathis, W. A. (Assistant Corporation Counsel) to Almet F. Jenks (Corporation Counsel), 1893 (Box 217, Folder 38)
  - Menorah Monthly Magazine, 1893 (Box 217, Folder 39)
    Regarding religious tax exemption
  - Cheshire, Charles W. (Acting Secretary, Department of Assessment, 1894 (Box 217, Folder 40)
    Young Men's Christian Association assessment issue
  - Corwin, Halsey (Comptroller), 1894 (Box 217, Folder 41)
    Regarding city rental properties
  - Department of City Works, 1894 (Box 217, Folder 42)
    Includes Alfred T. White, R. M. Whiting, and Frank Lyman
  - Hinrichs, Frederick W. (Registrar of Arrears), 1894 (Box 217, Folder 43)
    Regarding Winthrop Park (now known as McGolrick Park); Ward 17 - Block 225 - Lot 35
  - Parsons, S. M., 1894 -1895 (Box 217, Folder 44)
    Regarding Powers estate
  - Smith, J. E. (Secretary, Department of Parks), 1894 (Box 217, Folder 45)
    Regarding taxation of Ridgewood Park
  - White, Alfred T. (Commissioner of City Works), 1894- 1895 (Box 217, Folder 46)
    Regarding water supply issues, 8th Ward streets, Greene Ave. relief sewer, repaving Ross St., and Union Elevated Railroad Company's 5th Ave.and 36th St. station
  - Barrow, Clarence A. (Deputy Fire Commissioner), 1895 (Box 217, Folder 47)
    Regarding purchase of property on 4th Ave., near 6th St.
  - Benjamin, Joseph (City Clerk), 1895 (Box 217, Folder 48)
    Regarding the grading and paving of Manhattan Ave. and Ewen St.
  - Brooklyn and Brighton Beach Railroad Company, 1895 (Box 217, Folder 49)
  - Commissioners of Electrical Subways, 1895 (Box 217, Folder 50)
    Regarding electrolysis
  - Department of City Works, 1895 (Box 217, Folder 51)
    Regarding Market St. (now Euclid Ave.) water hydrants; Includes map of Cypress Hills and East New York
  - Dunnett, William J. (Deputy Clerk, City of New York Law Department), 1895 (Box 217, Folder 52)
    Regarding law clerk salaries
  - Lyman, Fred (Deputy Commissioner of City Works), 1895 (Box 217, Folder 53)
    Regarding 8th Ward opening maps
  - O'Dwyer, Edward F., 1895 (Box 217, Folder 54)
    Regarding back pay claims by Miller and Smith
  - Page, William H., Jr., 1895 (Box 217, Folder 55)
  - Piper, Mrs., 1895 (Box 217, Folder 56)
    Includes water bill for 314 22nd St.
  - West Brooklyn Land and Improvement Company, 1895 (Box 217, Folder 57)
    Regarding Board of Education agreement
  - Young, Charles R., 1895 (Box 217, Folder 58)
    Regarding Dean v. Queens
  - Hinrichs, Fred W., 1896 (Box 217, Folder 59)
    Related to East Side Park Land properties and Culyer foreclosures
  - Jones Oyster House, 1896 (Box 217, Folder 60)
  - Lamb, Albert E., 1896 (Box 217, Folder 61)
    Regarding the New York and Sea Beach Railway Company
  - Mac Krell, H.C., 1896 (Box 217, Folder 62)
  - Murphy, George L. (Clerk of Market), 1896 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    Regarding stables erection in Wallabout Market
  - Palmer, W. M. (Secretary to the Mayor), 1896 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    Regarding 26th Ward assessments
  - U. S. Weather Service, 1896 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    Regarding weather in February 1892
  - White, Alfred T. (Commissioner of City Works), 1896 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    Regarding wharfage on Bowne St.
  - Feitner, Thomas L. (Department of Taxes and Assessments), 1897 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    Regarding the assessment roll for the Town of Middletown, County of Richmond
  - General Correspondence, 1897 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    Includes Wallabout Market lease
  - Hawley, William H., Jr. (Assistant Clerk, Assembly Chamber, State of New York), 1897 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Shortt, William Allaire, 1897 (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Vail, E. G., Jr., 1897 (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - Arbona, A., 1898 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    Regarding opening Pennsylvania Ave., from Eastern Parkway to Belmont Ave.
  - Associated Cycling Clubs of Long Island, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    Regarding poor street conditions
  - Baker, William Cas (Queens County Sheriff), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 12)
  - Bedford Dispensary of Brooklyn, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 13)
  - Bell, Frank J. (Chief Deputy, Department of Taxes and Assessments), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 14)
  - Bowley, Frederick (President of the Borough of Queens), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 15)
  - Burger, Anthony J. and George W. Delap (Coroners of the Borough of Brooklyn), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 16)
  - Burr, Joseph, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 17)
  - City Magistrate's Court, First District, Second Division, City of New York, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 18)
    Regarding abandonment trials
  - Coler, Bird S. (Comptroller), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 19)
    Regarding Village of Lawrence school tuition, Town of Newton street improvement contract, voucher of James Powers, bond accounts of the City of Brooklyn, grade crossings over Manhattan Beach Railroad, Prospect Park assessments, claims in street openings, deficiencies in tax levy of Brooklyn, the claims of Thomas F. Fox and George H. Lawson, Kleinfelder property, Wallabout Market, and other matters
  - Collin, A., 1898 (Box 218, Folder 20)
    Regarding railroad construction Avenue C and East 37th St.; Avenue C is now known as Claredon Rd.
  - Comptroller's Office, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 21)
  - Cronyn, C. N. and M. (Law stenographers), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 22)
    Regarding work done for the 86th Street Pumping Station
  - Dalton, William (Commissioner of Water Supply), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 23)
    Regarding laying water mains on Park Pl., between Albany Ave. and Troy Ave., Brooklyn and Queens water rates, and water service revenue
  - Daly, Michael T., 1898 (Box 218, Folder 24)
    List of summonses
  - Department of Sewers, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 25)
    Regarding sewers contracts
  - Farrell, Thomas R. (Deputy Commissioner of Highways), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 26)
    Assessments for local improvements
  - Feitner, Thomas L. (Department of Taxes and Assessments Commissioner), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 27)
    Regarding jury lists
  - Fitch, Joseph (Deputy Commissioner Water Supply, Borough of Queens), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 28)
    Regarding Queens pumping stations insurance
  - Grout, Edward M. (President of the Borough of Brooklyn), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 29)
    Regarding a railroad on Gravesend Ave. (now McDonald Ave.)
  - Jasper, William H. (Board of Assessors), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 30)
  - Jenks, Almet F., 1898 (Box 218, Folder 31)
    Regarding consolidation of the City of Brooklyn with New York City
  - Kane, James (Commissioner of Sewers), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 32)
    Regarding 29th Ward sewer assessments and the Village of New Brighton Sewer system
  - Kearney, Henry S. (Commissioner of Public Buildings, Lighting and Supplies), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 33)
    Regarding extinguishing unnecessary gas lights in the 30th Ward of Brooklyn; Includes Kings County Gas and Illuminating Company and Brooklyn Union Gas Company bills
  - Keating, James P. (Commissioner of Highways), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 34)
    Regarding County Road System in Queens, Includes blueprints for connection of the Coney Island and Brooklyn Railroad Company to the Nassau Brewing Company at Franklin Ave. and Dean St.; Also regarding the authority to open streets near public parks and highway inspector salaries
  - Lewis, N. P. (Department of Highways engineer), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 35)
    Regarding assessment abstracts and the Kings County Electric Light and Power Company
  - Moffett, James (Deputy Commissioner of the Water Supply for the Borough of Brooklyn), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 36)
  - Monteverde, William T. (Municipal Court Justice), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 37)
    Regarding method of obtaining a jury list; Includes John Purcell (Commissioner of Juries)
  - Protzmann and Seaton, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 38)
    Wallabout Market merchants
  - Rudd, Frank, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 39)
    Regarding tax sale and unpaid water rates
  - Scannell, John J. (Fire Commissioner), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 40)
    Regarding bond and mortgage on the property of Thomas Hickson, 85-89 -93 Russell St.
  - Simis, A., Jr. (Commissioner of Public Charities), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 41)
    Regarding burial expenses, aid to blind non-citizens, and civil service appointments and salary
  - Skinner, Charles R. (State Superintendent of Public Instruction), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 42)
    Regarding appointment of pupils to deaf and dumb institutions
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Company, 1898 (Box 218, Folder 43)
    Regarding assessments of O'Rourke Farm and McKane Farm for opening East 24th-East 25th Streets and Voorhies Ave.; Ward 31 - Blocks 430-434, and 456-461
  - Tyng, C. Rockland (Secretary, Department of Taxes and Assessment), 1898 (Box 218, Folder 44)
  - Board of Alderman, 1899 (Box 218, Folder 45)
    Regarding repaving assessments
  - Board of Alderman, Law Committee, 1899 (Box 218, Folder 46)
    Regarding sale of real estate
  - Board of Armory Commissioners, 1899 (Box 218, Folder 47)
  - Board of Assessors, 1899 (Box 218, Folder 48)
    Regarding 1898 assessments, and College Point sewer assessments
  - Board of City Record, 1899 (Box 218, Folder 49)
    Includes William A. Butler
  - Board of Public Improvements, 1899 (Box 218, Folder 50)
    Regarding grading and paving Grand St., Himrod St. improvement, obstructions at the foot of 65th St., and opening 62nd St.
  - Brower, George V. (Commissioner of Parks for the Boroughs of Brooklyn and Queens), 1899 (Box 218, Folder 51)
    Regarding property to be taken for Shore Drive (now Bay Ridge Ave.) - Anton Wick (or Weck) (5th Ave. and 67th St.), and Red Hook Park
  - Burger, Anthony J. and George W. Delap (Coroners of the Borough of Brooklyn), 1899 (Box 218, Folder 52)
  - Carroll, Thomas (Accountant, Police Department), 1899 (Box 218, Folder 53)
  - Cochran, Alfred, 1899-1900 (Box 218, Folder 54)
    Regarding purchase of property in Rosedale (Long Island) for acqueduct
  - Coler, Bird S. (Comptroller), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    Regarding bill of A. W. Shephard, Joseph A. McGarry contract, application of Hans C. Pfalzgraf, Ryan and McFarren contract, remittance of state tax 1898, application of Industrial School Association, sewer assessments, Albert E. Donovan contract, John F. Maillie contract, Brooklyn Publishers Association, the Village of Edgewater and the Union Trust Company of New York mortgage, Sandford and Company-Butler St. asphalting, the Schluchtner Brothers claim, Neptune Ave. opening bonds, application of Henry W. Lee, the Inebriates Home of Kings County, the application of John Grimm, grading and paving 44th and 46th St., taxes on City property in Freeport, the Edison Electric Company judgement, Surf Ave. assessments, excise money paid to the police pension fund, Brooklyn Maternity contract, claim assignments of the deceased (Tillotson), the will of Augustus Graham, and other matters
  - Dalton, William (Commissioner of Water Supply), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    Regarding Vanderveer Park water supply (Flatbush), Queens County water bills, coal contracts, land acquisitions for additional pipe conduits, and Brooklyn Children's Aid Society water rates
  - Eddy Valve Company, 1899 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Feitner, Thomas L. (President, Department of Taxes and Assessments), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    Regarding assessments for flagging
  - Gibson, F. M. (Deputy Commissioner of Street Cleaning, Borough of Manhattan), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    Regarding advertising street cleaning contracts
  - Gormly, John L. J., 1899 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    Bill for Smith case
  - Grout, Edward M. (President of the Borough of Brooklyn), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    Regarding assessments and dedicating street land
  - Helland, E. Bartlette (Treasurer of the Village of Freeport), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    Regarding the tax sale of City property
  - Holahan, Maurice F. (President, Board of Public Improvements), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    Regarding public lighting
  - Kane, James (Commissioner of Sewers), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    Petition of James N. Egbert and the Jewett Ave. and Cherry Lane sewer system, Reid Ave. (now Malcolm X Blvd.) sewer construction contract with Daniel J. Creem, sewer assessments, and Gowanus Canal dredging
  - Kearney, Henry S. (Commissioner of Public Buildings, Lighting and Supplies), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    Regarding coal contracts and building on Gates Ave. (near Marcy Ave.) and appointing the keeper of the Hall of Records
  - Keating, James P. (Commissioner of Highways), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    Regarding 8th Ward Improvement Act, street repair contracts, pavement contractors repairing streets damaged by escaping gas, and squatters on Park Pl.
  - Keiley, John D. (President, Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School for Boys), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 13)
  - Kimball, John W. (Treasurer of the County of Kings), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    Regarding Inebriates' House
  - Lantry, Francis J. (Commissioner of Correction), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    Regarding housing U.S. prisoners in the Kings County Penitentiary and Nassau County prisoner agreement
  - Lederle, Ernst J. (Commissioner of Health), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 16)
    Regarding sewage disposal in Coney Island
  - Little, Joseph J. (President, Department of Education), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 17)
    Regarding the schedule of salaries adopted by the School Board, and purchasing supplies
  - Mackellar, John (Deputy Chief of Police), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 18)
    Regarding Long Island Railroad Company employees damaging Forest Park property
  - Moffett, James (Deputy Commissioner of the Water Supply for the Borough of Brooklyn), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 19)
    Village of Freeport property taxes
  - Probasco, Samuel K. (Chief Clerk), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 20)
    Joseph H. Hollands
  - Ross, A. W. (Deputy Superintendent of School Buildings, Borough of Brooklyn), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 21)
    Regarding the closing of Public School No. 7
  - Scannell, John J. (Fire Commissioner), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 22)
    Regarding bell ringers and pensions
  - Shea, John L. (Commissioner of Bridges), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 23)
  - Simis, A., Jr. (Commissioner of Public Charities), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 24)
    Regarding Kings County Hospital contract, and abandonment case
  - Somers, Daniel M. and Charles F. Phillips (Committee on Sites of Brooklyn Public Library), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 25)
  - Whitney, D. D., Jr. (Assistant Corporation Counsel), 1899 (Box 219, Folder 26)
    Montauk Club
  - Bell, James D. (Commission of the New East River Bridge), 1900 (Box 219, Folder 27)
    Regarding the Williamsburg Bridge
  - Berrick, Solon (Deputy Supervisor, City Record), 1900 (Box 219, Folder 28)
  - Board of Alderman, Law Committee, 1900 (Box 219, Folder 29)
    Regarding railroad tunnel under East River
  - Board of Assessors, 1900 (Box 219, Folder 30)
    Opening 16th Ave., 85th St., and Park Pl.
  - Board of Estimate and Apportionment, 1900 (Box 219, Folder 31)
    Regarding Noll St. quit-claim deed, and Flatbush Water Works Company property
  - Board of Public Improvements, 1900 (Box 219, Folder 32)
    Regarding acquisition of the Flatbush Water Supply Company
  - Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School for Boys, 1900- 1903 (Box 219, Folder 33)
  - Brower, George V. (Commissioner of Parks for the Boroughs of Brooklyn and Queens), 1900 (Box 219, Folder 34)
    Acquiring the property of Grace Methodist Episcopal Church of Bay Ridge for Bay Ridge Parkway
  - Butler, William A. (Secretary, Board of City Records), 1900 (Box 219, Folder 35)
  - Chambers, Jared J. (Secretary, Board of Magistrates), 1900 (Box 219, Folder 36)
  - Coler, Bird S. (Comptroller), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    Regarding taxes on city property in Freeport, Board of Commissioners for the Improvement of Brooklyn Heights, former Samuel S. Stryker property in Gravesend, law library dispursements, the Queens County Board of Supervisors, tax sale certificates, sewer construction, court payrolls, Staten Island Water Company contract, John Klein quit-claim deed (Noll St. and Bushwick Ave.), turnpike roads, and other matters
  - Dalton, William (Commissioner of Water Supply), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Regarding taxes on city property in Freeport, water rates in Brooklyn and Queens, water main connection for school at Rockaway Ave. and Blake Ave., the Woodside Water Company contract, Hempstead water bills, and water meter dispute (68 John St.)
  - Dooling, Peter J. (Acting and Deputy Commissioner of Public Buildings, Lighting and Supplies), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    Regarding Kings County requisitions
  - Feitner, Thomas L. (President, Department of Taxes and Assessments), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Grout, Edward M. (President of the Borough of Brooklyn), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    Regarding construction of an awning at Lafayette Ave. and Tompkins Ave.
  - Guggenheimer, Randolph (President of the Council), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Haslin, Jas. H. (Deputy Commissioner of Water Supply), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    Regarding Vanderveer Park water supply (Flatbush)
  - Holahan, Maurice F. (President, Board of Public Improvements), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    Regarding street numbering in Far Rockaway
  - Kane, James (Commissioner of Sewers), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    Regarding labor law violations and dredging slips at the foot of Joralemon St. and Degraw St.
  - Kearney, Henry S. (Commissioner of Public Buildings, Lighting and Supplies), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    Regarding electric lights in Prospect Park South, the museum building, Flatbush Gas Company contract, and other matters
  - Keating, James P. (Commissioner of Highways), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    Regarding paving 2nd Ave. and railroad tracks, and tracks crossing over West 1st St., West 3rd St., and West 5th St., and the Cranford Company paving contract
  - Lantry, Francis J. (Commissioner of Correction), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 12)
    Regarding case of George Ketchum
  - Nagle, Percival E. (Commissioner of Street Cleaning), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    Regarding newspaper announcement contracts and Robert H. Taylor property
  - Scannell, John J. (Fire Commissioner), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    Regarding pensions for widows and orphans and taxes on foreign fire insurance companies
  - Simis, A. (Commisioner of Public Charities for the Boroughs of Brooklyn and Queens), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 15)
    Regarding headstone contracts and other matters
  - Stryker, William H., 1900 (Box 220, Folder 16)
    Regarding award for Lot 30 taken in the opening of Emmons Ave.
  - Van Buren, Robert (Engineer in Charge, Department of Water Supply), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 17)
    Village of Freeport property taxes and other matters
  - Walde, George E. (Commissioner of Records, Kings County), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 18)
  - Ward, Edward G. (Superintendent of Schools, Borough of Brooklyn), 1900 (Box 220, Folder 19)
    Regarding principals voting on teacher salaries
  - Board of Assessors, 1901 (Box 220, Folder 20)
    29th Ward sewer assessments
  - Board of Public of Improvements, 1901 (Box 220, Folder 21)
    Regarding street openings and Union St. railroad crossing
  - Brower, George V. (Commissioner of Parks for the Boroughs of Brooklyn and Queens), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 22)
    Regarding Dyker Beach Park
  - Coler, Bird S. (Comptroller), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 23)
    Regarding Humboldt St. sewer property damage claims, acquiring property on McKibben St. for school purposes, acquiring property on Prospect Pl. and Park Pl. for school purposes, East Side Lands mortgages, state taxes levied against Kings County, the Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, firemen salary claims, sewer property damage claims, Emmons Ave. opening, Wallabout Market, and other matters
  - Dalton, William (Commissioner of Water Supply), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 24)
    Regarding pumping station at Foster's Meadow in Nassau County (Elmont)
  - Dougherty, J. Hampden, 1901 (Box 220, Folder 25)
    Regarding water supply and Forest Park (Queens)
  - Grout, Edward M. (President of the Borough of Brooklyn), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 26)
    Regarding repaving Varick St.
  - Haviland, C. Augustus, 1901 (Box 220, Folder 27)
    Regarding removal of railroad tracks on Atlantic Ave.
  - Loud, George B. (Inspector General, Grand Army of the Republic), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 28)
    Regarding compensation of lecturers in public schools
  - Moffett, James (Deputy Commissioner of the Water Supply for the Borough of Brooklyn), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 29)
    Regarding salary payments
  - Municipal Civil Service Commission, 1901 (Box 220, Folder 30)
  - Murphy, Michael C. (Police Commissioner), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 31)
    Regarding telegraph operator pensions
  - O'Brien, Miles M. (President, Board of Education), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 32)
    Regarding the Free Lecture System, acquiring property for schools, and teacher salaries
  - Robb, Thomas (Eccentric Engineers in the Borough of Brooklyn), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 33)
    Regarding wages paid to city employees
  - Scannell, John J. (Fire Commissioner), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 34)
    Regarding Flatlands Fire Department
  - Van Sirlen, James C., 1901 (Box 220, Folder 35)
  - Van Wyck, Robert A. (Mayor), 1901 (Box 220, Folder 36)
    Regarding Edison Electric Illuminating Company underground conduit system assessment
  - Board of Commissioners of the Sinking Fund, 1902 (Box 220, Folder 37)
  - Board of Health, 1902 (Box 220, Folder 38)
    Regarding cattle slaughter
  - Burlingham, Charles C. (President, Board of Education), 1902 (Box 220, Folder 39)
    Regarding York St. property
  - Cowen, Philip (Supervisor, City Record), 1902 (Box 220, Folder 40)
  - Dike, Norman S. (Sheriff), 1902 (Box 220, Folder 41)
    Regarding prison electrification
  - Grout, Edward M. (Comptroller), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    Regarding sewer overflow claims, street openings, Hinsdale St. assessments, York St. school site, Wallabout and Brooklyn Toll Bridge Company Road, old turnpike properties, County of Kings state taxes, Surf Ave. assessments, and other matters
  - Hynes, Thomas W. (Commissioner of Corrections), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Kaufmann, Edward, 1902 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    Regarding Bay Ridge Free Library and Fort Hamilton Free Library
  - Lindenthal, Gustav (Commissioner of Bridges), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    Regarding jurisdiction over Liberty St. (today part of Cadman Plaza) and repaving roadway approachs to Brooklyn Bridge
  - Logan Club, 1902 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    Includes legal notes on verso
  - Lumis, William (Chairman, Committee on Buildings, Department of Education), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    Regardinging 22 to 46 Locust St.
  - McDermott, James W. and Charles J., 1902 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    Regarding Donohue property at Springfield, Long Island (Queens)
  - McDonald, Albert G., 1902 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    Regarding Middagh St. and Poplar St. school site
  - Monroe, Robert Brier (Commissioner of Water Supply, Gas and Electricity), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    Regarding Hempstead property assessment and fire service charges
  - Osborn, Thomas D. (Secretary, Board of City Magistrates), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    Regarding police clerk payroll
  - Partridge, John H. (Police Commissioner), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 11)
    Regarding duty of police in magistrates' matter
  - Powers, Joseph P. (Board of Representatives, Rockaway Beach Fire Department), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - Redfield, William C. (Commissioner of Public Works), 1902 (Box 221, Folder 13)